(Howard:)All right, if you're gonna
calmly make excellent points,
(Howard:)then I don't know
if I want to talk to you.
(Howard:)Okay. I get it.
(Howard:)And it's sweet that
you're worried about me,
(Howard:)but I can take care of myself.
(Bernadette:)I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about me.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to go through
this pregnancy listening
(Bernadette:)to you complain about Sheldon
driving you crazy
(Bernadette:)more than you already do.
(Howard:)Here we go with
the ironclad logic again.
(Bernadette:)You've tried to work
with him before.
(Bernadette:)It hasn't gone well.
(Bernadette:)Why is this time
gonna be any different?
Is the fetus helping you?
'Cause that's cheating.
(Raj:)(phone rings)
(Raj:)Hello?
CLAIRE: Hey, Raj.
(Claire:)It's Claire. How are you?
(Raj:)Hi. I'm good. Really good.
(Raj:)Well, I don't know
why I said “really good.”
(Raj:)I'm just regular good.
(Raj:)I really just wanted
to sound confident.
And that “really”
was a real “really,”
not a fake “really”
like the first “really.”
(Claire:)Really?